National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Issues Files, 1961-2011; 3; 8.4 cubic ft.
  The NOW-NYS Issues series contains journal articles, newspaper clippings, legislative and task force memoranda, committee and research reports, newsletters, leaflets and fliers, correspondence with NOW-NYS presidents and testimony at public hearings and legal proceedings. The series also contains posters and announcements of events, state and federal laws and proposed bills relating to discrimination and gender bias in education, labor, politics, abortion, women's health care, birth control issues, domestic relations (1981-1985), the Equal Rights Amendment, lesbian and gay rights, and the greater women's movement.
  - Abortion (1 of 4), 1972-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abortion (2 of 4), 1972-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abortion (3 of 4), 1972-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abortion (4 of 4), 1972-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abortion and Mortality Wars, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abortion Funding, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abortion-Newsclippings, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Abortion Pamphlets, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abused Women (1 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abused Women (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adoption and Foster Care, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action (1 of 3), 1972-1982; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action (2 of 3), 1972-1982; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action (3 of 3), 1972-1982; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aged Women, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agriculture Bill, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alcoholism, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - A New NOW, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anti-Choice, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Anti-Trafficking, 1993-1994; 1999; 2007-2009; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Assertiveness Training, 1972-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Awards of Legal Fees in Matrimonial Actions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bella Abzug for Congress, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bias-Related Violence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Big Mountain Relocation, 1986; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Birth Control (1 of 2), 1974-1979; 1981-1982; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Birth Control (2 of 2), 1974-1979; 1981-1982; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Breast Cancer, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Breast Implants, 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn-Queens Chapter Task Force Report, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cameras in the Courtroom, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Campus Legislation- Sexual Assault, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Casino Gambling (1 of 2), 1992; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Casino Gambling (2 of 2), 1992; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Central Park Rape Coalition, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cervical Cancer, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chana and Simon Taub, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Charitable Choice, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Child Abuse, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Child Abuse and Safety, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Child Birth, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Child Custody and Abuse, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Child Support (1 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Child Support (2 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Childcare, 1970-1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Childcare- Taskforce, 1986; 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Child Support Enforcement, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Citizens with Disabilities, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights Act, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Combating Racism, 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Combating Racism Guides, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Comic Books, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Comparable Worth, 1991; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Computers, 1981; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Consciousness Raising, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Continuing Education, 1961-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cornell- Sexual Harassment Complaint Resolution, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Crime Victims, Crime, and Correction, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Daycare, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dineh Nation, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Discrimination in Education (1 of 5), 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Discrimination in Education (2 of 5), 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Discrimination in Education (3 of 5), 1963-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Discrimination in Education (4 of 5), 1963-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Discrimination in Education (5 of 5), 1963-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Discrimination in Education- Occupational Training (1 of 4), 1963-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in Education- Occupational Training (2 of 4), 1963-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in Education- Occupational Training (3 of 4), 1963-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in Education- Occupational Training (4 of 4), 1963-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Discrimination in Education- States Discrimination, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Discrimination in Education- Textbook Bias (1 of 2), 1965; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Discrimination in Education- Textbook Bias (2 of 2), 1965; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Discrimination in Education- Title IX (1 of 2), 1972-1976; 1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Discrimination in Education- Title IX (2 of 2), 1972-1976; 1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination in Employment (1 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Discrimination in Employment (2 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Discrimination in Employment (3 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Discrimination in Employment (4 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Discrimination in Employment (5 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Discrimination in Employment (6 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in Employment (7 of 7), 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in Higher Education (1 of 3), 1970-1976; 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in Higher Education (2 of 3), 1970-1976; 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Discrimination in Higher Education (3 of 3), 1970-1976; 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Discrimination on the Basis of Sexual Orientation: Assessment of the Law, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Divorce, 1970-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Divorce- Child Support and Child Custody, 1971-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Partnership, 1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Relations Law, 1996; 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Domestic Relations Task Force, 1996-1998; 2001; 2011 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Domestic Violence, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Domestic Violence and Incest, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Domestic Violence and Incest Task Force, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Early Childhood Education, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Electing Women to Office, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ending Violence Against Women, 1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Environment, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Equal Pay, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (1 of 2), 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (2 of 2), 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Task Force, 1991-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Euthanasia (Right to Die), 1973; 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fair Testing, 1987; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Family, 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Family Planning, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Family Planning Advocates, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Family Violence, 1976-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fathers' Rights, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Feminist, 1974-1975; 1979; 1982; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Literature (1 of 3), 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Feminist Literature (2 of 3), 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Feminist Literature (3 of 3), 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Feminist Literature- Bibliographies (1 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Feminist Literature- Bibliographies (2 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fetal Alcohol Syndrome, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Florida Citrus, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Choice Act, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Gender Equality, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Genetics, 1972; 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Global Feminism, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Guam, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Guidelines for Task Forces, 1979; 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Handicapped, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hate Crimes, 1992; 2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Health Aids and Substance Abuse, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Health Care, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Health Task Force, 1990; 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Hearst, Patty, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Hospital- Abortion Resources, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Housewives, 1970-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Human Rights Commission- County of Suffolk, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - International Commission on Human Rights, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - International Women's Year (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - International Women's Year (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Joint Custody (1 of 4), 1978-2005; Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Joint Custody (2 of 4), 1978-2005; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Joint Custody (3 of 4), 1978-2005; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Joint Custody (4 of 4), 1978-2005; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Joint Custody- Domestic Law and Abuse, 1995-1996; 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Judge Demarest, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Keupsak, Mary Anne, 1971-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Key Legislative Issues, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Labor Movement, 1970-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Lesbian Rights (1 of 2), 1980; 1989-1992; 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Lesbian Rights (2 of 2), 1980; 1989-1992; 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Lesbian Rights Summit, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Lesbian Rights Task Force, 1989-1992; 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Lesbian Task Force, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lesbianism (1 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lesbianism (2 of 2), 1970-1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lesbians and Gays in the Military, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Congress on the Issues, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Mandatory Arbitration, 1998; Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mario Cuomo, 1982; Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Matrimonial and Family Law Cases, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women, 1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Middle East Crisis, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Mike Sullivan, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Mobilization for Women's Rights, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - National Health Care, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - No Fault Divorces (1 of 3), 1982; 1990; 1997-1998; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - No Fault Divorces (2 of 3), 1982; 1990; 1997-1998; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - No Fault Divorces (3 of 3), 1982; 1990; 1997-1998; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - No Thanks Big Tobacco, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Non- Traditional Employment for Women, 1988; Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - NOW-NYS Young Feminist Task Force, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - NOW- On the Issues, 1987; 1991; 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - NOW- On the Issues- Lesbian Rights, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - NOW Opposition Statements, 1989; 1991-1992; 1997; 1999; 2005-2009 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NOW Priority Issues, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - NOW Support Statements (1 of 2), 1987; 1989-1992; 1996-1999; 2005; 2009 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - NOW Support Statements (2 of 2), 1987; 1989-1992; 1996-1999; 2005; 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Nursing, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NYS Education Department, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Objectification and Sexual Exploitation of Women and Girls, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Operation Rescue, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Osteoporosis, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Palm Beach Rape, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Parental Consent, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Parenting, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equality (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equality (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Politics, 1980; 1982; 1985; Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Politics of Religion, 1998; 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pornography, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pornography- Censorship, 1979; 1989-1992; 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Pornography Task Force, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Position on the Issue of Pornography, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Poverty, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Preserving the Right to Choose, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Preventative Health Care, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Proposed Orders of Consideration, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Racial Justice, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Rape (1 of 2), 1971-1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rape (2 of 2), 1971-1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Rape Sexual Assault Meeting the Crisis, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Repeal Restrictions in Federal Health Programs, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reproductive Health Equity Act, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Reproductive Rights, 1993; 1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Reproductive Rights Task Force, 1996; 1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Reproductive Rights- Update on Roe v. Wade, 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Saudi Arabia and Kuwait- Military Defense, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Senate Task Force on Family Equality, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Single Sex Education, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Sex Discrimination Against Women, 1972-1978; Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Sexism in Language, 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1992; 1994; 1998; Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Smoke Free, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Social Security, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Stalking, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Stereotypes- Gender, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Task Force Information, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Task Force Plans, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Task Force Plans, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Task Force Plans, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Task Force Plans, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Task Force Plans, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Task Force Plans, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Task Force Plans, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Task Force Proposals, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Task Force Proposals, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Task Force Reports, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Reports, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Task Force Reports, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Task Force Reports, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Task Force- Year End Report, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Teenage Pregnancy/Teenage Sex, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Toys and Toy making, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Trafficking, Prostitution, and Pornography- Task Force, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Trafficking and Women, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Violence Against Women, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Violence Against Women Act, 1991-1992; 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Visitation/Parenting Time, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Watch Out, Listen Up!, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Welfare, 1989; 1994-1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Reform, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Witchcraft, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Women After Prison, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Women and AIDS, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Women and Religion, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Women as Consumers, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Women at Work, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Women Authors, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Women Calendar, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Women Consultants, 1974; 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Women History, 1969-1976; 1980; 1982; 1985; Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Women in Business, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Women in Film, 1971-1976; 1979; 1982 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Women in Healthcare, 1973; 1975-1981; Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Women in Literature, 1972; 1974; 1979; 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Women in Mass Media, 1969-1972; 1974-1975; 1979 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Women in Politics (1 of 2), 1973-1985; Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Women in Politics (2 of 2), 1973-1985; Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Women in Prison, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Women in Prison- Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Women in Sports, 1974; 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Women in Television, 1970; 1972-1975; Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Women in the Theater, 1971-1976; 1978; Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Women- Mental Health, 1970-1972; 1974-1976; 1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Women Musicians, 1975-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Women of Color Rights, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Women of Color Task Force, 1989-1991; 1993; Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Women- Pensions and Insurance, 1963; 1972-1977; Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Women, Work, and Poverty, 1989-1990; 1996 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Women's Centers, 1971; 1974; 1976-1977; 1979-1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Women's Employment, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Women's Issues- Public Hearing on Working Women and Caregiving, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Women's Liberation Movement, 1970-1978; 1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Women's Reproductive Domain Task, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Women's Right to Know, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Women's Sexual Behavior, 1972-1976; 1978; Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Working Women (1 of 3), 1966-1967; 1969-1976; 1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Working Women (2 of 3), 1966-1967; 1969-1976; 1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Working Women (3 of 3), 1966-1967; 1969-1976; 1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Young Feminist Meeting, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Lobbyist Files, 1972-2011; 4; 8.0 cubic ft.
  The NOW-NYS Lobbyists' files contain correspondence, lobbyists' notes on contacts with politicians and other lobbying groups, testimony, depositions from public hearings, bill proposals, and memoranda relating to the women's liberation movement in New York. Issues covered include NOW-NYS's responses to legislative bills concerning employment, abortion, child abuse, domestic violence, gay and lesbian rights, marriage and divorce, rape prevention, reproductive rights, and sex equity in education. Correspondents include the lobbyists and NOW-NYS presidents, Political Action questionnaires, and letters to Senators and other New York State politicians.
  - 100 Day Legislative Action Plan for Women's Civil Rights, Health, and Economic Empowerment, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The 1993 Citizen's Guide to the NYS Legislature (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abortion, 1977-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abortion Consent, 1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abstinence Education, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adult Education Plan, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adultery, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AFLCO - Pay Equality, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Age of Support, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alimony, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alimony and Child Support, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Analysis Updates, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Animal Abuse, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Violence Healthcare, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Assembly, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Assembly, 1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Assembly, 1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Assembly and Senate Calendar of Bills and Committee Agenda, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Assembly Member Directory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Assembly Speaker Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assembly Voting Records- Discrimination On The Basis of Sexual Orientation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beatrice Kachuck's Letters, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bias Crimes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bias-Relayed Violence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bliley Amendment, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bills, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bills, A5906, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bills, A7986, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bills, S8485, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bills- General, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bills NOW Opposes, 1987; 1990-2000; 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bills NOW Supports (1 of 2), 1988; 1991-1992; 1994-1998; 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bills NOW Supports (2 of 2), 1988; 1991-1992; 1994-1998; 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bills to be Reviewed, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Birth Control and Privacy, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Budget, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Budget Priorities, 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Budget Priorities, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Calendar of Bills, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - California's Gender Parity Bill, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Campaign Finances, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Candidate List, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Casino Gambling, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Censorship, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Chemical Agents and Weapons, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Child Abuse and Maltreatment, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Child Custody Disputes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Child Protection, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Child Sexual Abuse, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Child Support (1 of 2), 1981-1982; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Child Support (2 of 2), 1981-1982; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Child Support Guidelines, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Child Support Standards Act, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Childcare, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Childcare Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Childcare- Services, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Sexual Offense, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - City Criminal Court Act, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1991, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights- Sexual Orientation, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Client Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Coalition for Choice, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commercialized Child- Bearing Prevention Act, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Commission On Child Support, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Commissions, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee Agendas (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Committee Agendas (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Children and Families, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Transportation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Community Outreach Program, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Comparable Worth, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Conception and Human Life Bill, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Conception and Insurance Companies, 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Consecutive Sentencing, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Coopersmith vs. Gold, 1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Court Restricting, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Crime Companion Act, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Criminal Court Act, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Daily Notes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Daniel P. Moynihan, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Data Files (1 of 4), Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Data Files (2 of 4), Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Data Files (3 of 4), Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Data Files (4 of 4), Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Daycare, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Discrimination In Employment, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Divorce, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Divorce Legal Fees, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Domestic Relations Bill, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Domestic Relations Law, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Relations Law- Weinstein, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Domestic Violence - Bills (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Domestic Violence - Bills (2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Early Services For Developmentally Disabled Infants and Toddlers, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Education (1 of 2), 1977-1979; 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)